[
  {
    "question": "1. Which planet is known as the Red Planet?",
    "choices": ["Earth", "Mars", "Jupiter", "Venus"],
    "fiftyFifty": "Jupiter",
    "answer": "Mars"
  },
  {
    "question": "2. What is the capital city of Thailand?",
    "choices": ["Chiang Mai", "Bangkok", "Phuket", "Ayutthaya"],
    "fiftyFifty": "Ayutthaya",
    "answer": "Bangkok"
  },
  {
    "question": "3. Which animal is known as the King of the Jungle?",
    "choices": ["Elephant", "Tiger", "Lion", "Giraffe"],
    "fiftyFifty": "Tiger",
    "answer": "Lion"
  },
  {
    "question": "4. How many continents are there on Earth?",
    "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
    "fiftyFifty": "6",
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "5. What is H2O commonly known as?",
    "choices": ["Fire", "Oil", "Water", "Salt"],
    "fiftyFifty": "Oil",
    "answer": "Water"
  },
  {
    "question": "6. Which programming language is primarily used for Android apps?",
    "choices": ["Python", "Java", "C++", "HTML"],
    "fiftyFifty": "C++",
    "answer": "Java"
  },
  {
    "question": "7. What is the largest ocean in the world?",
    "choices": ["Indian Ocean", "Pacific Ocean", "Atlantic Ocean", "Arctic Ocean"],
    "fiftyFifty": "Atlantic Ocean",
    "answer": "Pacific Ocean"
  },
  {
    "question": "8. Which instrument has black and white keys?",
    "choices": ["Guitar", "Violin", "Piano", "Flute"],
    "fiftyFifty": "Violin",
    "answer": "Piano"
  },
  {
    "question": "9. Which country invented pizza?",
    "choices": ["France", "Japan", "Italy", "USA"],
    "fiftyFifty": "France",
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "question": "10. Which is the fastest land animal?",
    "choices": ["Horse", "Cheetah", "Wolf", "Leopard"],
    "fiftyFifty": "Leopard",
    "answer": "Cheetah"
  }
]
